Guide to the West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers, ca 1979-1982.
West Coast Punk and New Wave Club flyers,
- Fliers and posters, 1978-1989
  - Mutants. Dead Kennedys, 1978-09-02; Illustrated with male face (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Iron House, Undated; Montage of prison cell images superimposed over quote of Lu Hsun (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Invertebrates, 1976-06-13-1982-06-13; Image of man and Scotch glass (Box 2, Folder 8)
    At Club Generic
  - Thunder Crack!, 1976-06-18-1982-06-19; Images from film (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Directed by Kurt McDowell. At Roxie Cinema.